This is a quick primer as to what all things close captions are not capable of doing.
In other words, please read this before you ask me why X and Y actions/events aren't captioned.

Like the Steam guide says, close captions are effectively a speech bubble that stays at the bottom of the screen. Things that the classes say can have a line of text assigned to them to show up in this speech bubble.

That being said, lets get to the point. Here are the things you can't caption right now:

 * Class walking/jumping/shooting X weapon
 * Class dying
 * Team-specific captions

And if you want to know *why* most of these are impossible, please check the "More importantly, what CAN'T I do?" section of the Steam guide, available online here: http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=167785751